// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is the commercial capital of Sri Lanka?",
    answer: "Colombo",
    options: [
      "Kandy",
      "Jaffna",
      "Colombo",
      "Anuradhapura"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the currency of Sri Lanka?",
    answer: "Rupee",
    options: [
      "Rupiah",
      "Pound",
      "Escudo",
      "Rupee"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What animal appears on the flag of Sri Lanka?",
    answer: "Lion",
    options: [
      "Elephant",
      "Lion",
      "Tiger",
      "Deer"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is the name of the annual festival held at the Temple of the Tooth Relic in Kandy, Sri Lanka?",
    answer: "Esala perahera",
    options: [
      "New year festival",
      "wesak perahara",
      "Esala perahera",
      "Poson poya day"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which one of the following activities can you NOT do during a trip to Sri Lanka?",
    answer: "Snow Skiing",
    options: [
      "Spelunking",
      "Whitewater Rafting",
      "Snow Skiing",
      "eHot Air Balloon Rides"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is the name of the famous beach in Sri Lanka where you can spot blue whales?",
    answer: "Mirissa",
    options: [
      "Mirissa",
      "Nilaweli",
      "Unawatuna",
      "Hikkaduwa"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What is the name of the beach in Sri Lanka where you can go snorkeling and see colorful fish and sea turtles?",
    answer: "Nilaweli beach",
    options: [
      "Mirissa",
      "Nilaweli beach",
      "Hikkaduwa",
      "Unawatuna"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What is the purpose of the Pinnawala Elephant Orphanage?      ",
    answer: "To provide a sanctuary for orphaned and injured elephants that have been rescued from the wild.",
    options: [
      "To provide entertainment for tourists visiting Sri Lanka",
      "To raise funds for elephant conservation efforts in Sri Lanka.",
      "To provide a breeding facility for captive elephants.",
      "To provide a sanctuary for orphaned and injured elephants that have been rescued from the wild."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "what are some of the popular tourist attractions that visitors can explore in the ancient city  Anuradhapura?",
    answer: "The Sri Maha Bodhi tree, ancient temples and palaces",
    options: [
      "The Sri Maha Bodhi tree, ancient temples and palaces",
      "National parks and wildlife sanctuaries",
      "Tea plantations and scenic train rides",
      "Beaches and surfing spots"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What are some of the notable ruins and sites to visit in Polonnaruwa?",
    answer: "The Royal Palace, Council Chamber, Gal Vihara, and various temples and stupas. ",
    options: [
      "The Yala National Park, and the Adam's Peak.",
      "The Royal Palace, Council Chamber, Gal Vihara, and various temples and stupas. ",
      "The Dambulla Cave Temple, and the Sigiriya Rock Fortress.",
      "The Nissanka Latha Mandapaya."
    ]
  },
  
];